Kind of like me and my boy Brandon Victor Dixon got to go to the US Open. Thanks to Heineken
We've arrived
We caught a little bit of the match in some random seats because they let us but then we went to the Heineken suite and boy
It was sweet. Look at that spread
The mac and cheese is actually legit and who wouldn't love a tennis ball cookie
My first professional tennis match, they was hitting that ball. Between matches we actually walked around and got to see just like the
Grounds and let me tell you the US Open is not playing with y'all. The namesake Arthur Ashe and of course Althea Gibson black folks is everywhere in tennis
Hey Coco!
Okay, so we just realized that Tiafoe is actually playing the next match so we're actually going to stick around
Okay, Heineken, thank you for bringing me to my first US Open. We had a blast
Tennis